JOANNA CHUNG

BILINGUAL DIGITAL ACCOUNT COORDINATOR/MANAGER

INFO

PHONE

6478798870

EMAIL

joannac95@gmail.com

SKILLS

Ability to Organize Own Work

• • • •

Customer Service

• • • •

Microsoft Excel

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Microsoft Office

••••

Client Management

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Confident and Friendly Manner

••••

Leadership and Teamwork

• • • • 0

LANGUAGES

French

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

English

••••

Kreole

••••

HOBBIES

Artist in many ways: Photography, Drawing, Graphic and Web Design, Creative Writing and Martial Arts (Muay Thai & BJJ)

PROFILE

My first hand customer experience for two years has made me such a better and wholesome person.

My passion for languages was quenched as a university French TA for students around my age or much older as well as working on some translation at my current job

My patience and stress tolerance have been constantly challenged while working with clients, but no matter how tough, the feeling that I did a great job and left my clients happy is worth it all.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Bilingual Account Coordinator, Elite Digital Inc.

North York

Sep 2017 - Present

Currently coordinating any program that is contest related. I'm also co-managing all of our Pepsi and Agropur accounts. As for the fulfilment of the programs, it all falls into my hands.

Front of House/Barista, SOMA Chocolatemaker

Toronto

May 2015 - Sep 2017

At the distillery location, I was one of the front of house staff as well as barista. Quickly worked my way to the top as one of the fastest and efficient employee, building a strong bond with our regular customers as well as new ones.

French Monitor & TA, Glendon College, York University

North York

Sep 2014 - Oct 2015

I attended regular classes to assist professors and was responsible of the last hours of all the classes. Outside classes, I had office hours for students needing guidance and practice at the "Salon Francophone" which also offers activities towards their credits.

Assistant in the Translation Dept., York University

North York

Jan 2016 - Apr 2017

Mostly filing tasks, phone calls and responding to student emails.

EDUCATION

Glendon College, York University, B.A.

North York

Sep 2014 - Jul 2017

Started my first year with an Undeclared major. I liked every field, from math and stats to philosophy of law and sociology to literature and linguistics. It was hard for me to pick a major, so I decided to have a taste of everything. Finally decided to major in French Studies and to have an advantage thanks to my bilingualism.

Ehàna Ctata Casandan, Cahaal Cartificata

chrome-extension://nlipoenfbbikpbjkfpfillcgkoblgpmj/edit.html

(S.C.) & Higher School Certificate (H.S.C.)

Ebene, Mauritius

Jan 2007 - Dec 2013

I was ranked 1st in school in my class year in French and 10th at national level in Travel and Tourism.

INTERNSHIPS

Auditor, Ernst & Young

Ebène, Mauritius

Jan 2014 - May 2014

Stock Inventory and Auditing for several clients like the Duty Free Stores of the island's airport as well as big grocery stores.

REFERENCES

References available upon request